Richie!
- Right on time.
- Hey. You're the lawyer?
Ron Laflamme. Great to meet you.
All right, homeboy. Pop a squat.
Start autographing by the flags.
Lot of paper to get through.
So, what do you think?
About?
Jeannie. She's pretty hot, right?
Oh. Yeah. No, she's... She's very pretty.
Yeah, she is.
Oh, we're doing that. Ok.
So yo, Peter tells me you're
popping your cherry with this.
So let me just walk you through it.
That stuff you're signing gives you
the convertible note for funding
and establishes you and Peter Gregory
as the board members of Pied Piper,
incorporated in the State of Delaware.
Ok. Why Delaware?
Rich, Rich. Lawyer, not lawyer. I got you.
So, Peter Gregory, big fan of you.
- Oh.
- He invited you to his toga party, right?
That's a big deal. Flo
Rida's gonna be there.
- You like Flo Rida?
- Should be fun.
- Yeah, I went to a lot...
- See this guitar?
Sergei and Larry from Google signed it.
- Both of them. Right there.
- Mmm. Mm.
So, Pied Piper.
You're one of Peter's
compression plays, huh?
Uhh, one of? How many does he have?
Not too many. Like six or eight.
Ok. Why are there so many?
You know how sea turtles
have a shit-ton of babies
because most of them die on
their way down to the water?
Peter just wants to make sure that
his money makes it to the ocean.
But it seems like you
got your shit together.
A lot of these guys come in here
and they can do all of
the engineering stuff
but they get all hung up on technicalities.
They can't just tell you what
their vision for the company is.
Those guys are so fucked.
It's like you need both
halves of the brain, right?
The Jobs and the Wozniak.
The ying and the yang.
Oh. I think it's "yin".
- "Yin"?
- Yeah.
- Like "yin and yan?"
- No. Like yin and yang.
No. It's ying and yang, they're opposites.
So, Pied Piper, drop it on me. What is it?
Well, we started off as a music app.
- Yuck.
- Yeah. Gross. Ugh.
But we've,
uh, we've pivoted since then.
Uh-oh. To what?
Well, our weissman scores are
consistently high across all media,
audio, video, meta-data.
Actually, that's not true. We've
had some trouble encoding 3D video.
I think it's because the pixels change
value differently
than conventional...
☯Synced & Corrected by Seppuku17☯
❃www.addic7ed.com❃
Just look at the flow diagram, dude.
No, the filter bank is part
of the prediction loop.
What are you talking about,
this is lossless compression.
Oh, hey, Big Head, you were there.
Why did Richard use a DCT filter bank?
Oh. Um...
Not really sure. Richard tried
to explain some of this stuff
but a lot of it I didn't really understand,
so I'd kinda just nod and smile, you know?
Can you at least help us figure out
this insane DFT spider web he's using?
Dude, do you understand any of this?
I eat the fish.
I understand you eat the fish.
But when you clean the fish
you can't leave the fish head
and guts and shit in the sink.
Because the whole house
smells like a bait station.
So you gotta put it in the trash
and then take the trash out.
Do you understand?
Yes. I eat the fish.
Motherfuck!
Do you know how awkward it is to not
be able to describe your own company?
Like, I built Pied Piper
and you could see it
but I can't really
describe to you what it is
even though I kind of know where I'm going.
You do realize we quit working on
our own apps to work for you, right?
Shouldn't you more than "Kind
of know where you're going?"
Because that's basically what the CEO does.
I do. Sort of.
Ok, it's like trying to
tell someone how to get somewhere,
even though you don't really
know the exact address. Right?
Like, how do you do that? Because you
can't just say "Go to 415 elm street,"
because you don't even
know what that is. Right?
So you have to say, you know,
"Go straight down that big road
and take a right at the weird thing."
But, you can't describe
what that weird thing is
because you just know it
as a weird thing, you know,
in your head. You always have.
Is that weird thing in
your head an aneurysm?
Richard, I'm just gonna recap for a second,
um, you turned down ten million dollars
to be able to develop something that
you, as the head of the company,
can't even describe to another human being?
I say this only to motivate you.
Ok, so I have been instructed to remove you
from the list of employees
assigned to the Nucleus project.
You will no longer receive any
Nucleus related communications,
uh, file reports, or attend
any Nucleus meetings.
Any questions?
Uh, no. That's... That's pretty clear.
Great.
Am I being reassigned to something else?
Not that I am aware of. At this time. No.
Wait, so then am I being fired?
Because I have a three year
contract and my stock options...
Ok. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Nobody is being fired. Ok?
Look, a contract is a contract.
You know. You've got a contract. And I've
got a contract. We all have contracts.
And-and here at Hooli,
contracts are honored.
Um... yours and mine.
Everybody's. So, um...
Have I made that perfectly clear?
Yeah, no. That's clear.
But, when I come into work
tomorrow, what do I... do?
That is unclear. At this time.
Shoulda worn more than my
underwear and a bed sheet.
- Underwear? Pussy.
- Yeah. I'm with him.
This is the type of evening
that requires free-balling.
Oh. I'm gonna take my underwear off too.
Richard! Hey, you made it!
So Peter met with Laflamme
today and signed the paperwork,
which means Pied Piper
is officially launched.
Uh, why didn't you tell me about all the
other compression plays Peter was seeding?
What? No... because it's
nothing you need to worry about.
Because none of those other
companies have your vision.
- My vision?
- Exactly.
Speaking of which, Peter really
wants you to come in on Friday
to chat about big picture stuff.
You know, lay out your
vision in broad strokes.
- Broad strokes... For the vision of the...
- Uh-huh.
Well, uh, Pied Piper is
compression and we all know that.
So we don't need to talk about that...
but I could because I'm the CEO.
Pied Piper takes the data...
And... smaller. To smaller.
And, also, there's more.
- It compresses the data overall...
- Yeah, I...
Excuse me. See you Friday. Hi Tom.
Richard, pace yourself, buddy.
You know, I wish this was
Roman times. You know?
Life was simpler back then.
Simpler for you. I would have been a slave.
There's still time.
Cool costume. Where'd you get it?
Uhh...
Uh, my bed.
- You're funny!
- Oh.
I'm Brooke and this is my friend Anastasia.
Hi.
- Hi.
- What's up, guys?
Uh...
So-so-so, how do you know Peter Gregory?
- Oh, through work.
- Mm-hmm.
We're actresses.
Cool. Uh, what type of actressing you work?
Oh, we're working right now.
Our startup sources actors
to parties to liven things up
and get into conversations with
guests and be interested in them.
Oh. Neat.
So, uh, who else is paid to be here?
Pretty much anyone that's
over a seven is with us,
and anyone that's under a three is a guest.
- It's a really fun job. Plus,
- Yeah.
Um, I get to work with my boyfriend.
- - Yo, yo, party
people,
y'all ready to get crazy?
Is that Flo Rida?
- No idea.
- Y'all ready to take this party
to a whole 'nother level?
It's time to meet the
original O.G. Gangster,
cash money mobster.
Y'all put your hands
together for my brother!
The illest, the chillest, emperor
of Rome, big Pete Gregory!
He is the illest and the chillest?
Big Pete Gregory!
Thank you, Florida.
Welcome to the Peter Gregory foundation's
fourth annual orgy of caring.
The first three were fine.
I hope that you enjoy the party.
There is a second bar in back
where the line is much shorter.
Thank you. I'm finished.
That was very abrupt.
- So this is a rap concert?
- Yep.
Holy shit, look at Erlich!
How the fuck did he get up there?
Man. See, that's what I wish I had.
It's like, I don't have any...
- Game.
- Game, yes! That's it.
You know, I always knew
I was missing something
and then someone explained
to me the concept of game,
I remember very distinctly thinking,
"That's what I don't have. Game."
Sorry.
- Hello?
- What's up, Richie Rich?
Great seeing you last night, buddy.
Just wanted you to know I had my associate
draft up everything like we
talked about and it is all good.
Just emailed you the board consent
which appoints your new board member.
So just print it, sign it, get it
to Gregory to sign and it is donezo.
Uh, new board member, what?
It's in the pdf, you'll see.
All right, homey, I gotta
go. My enema guy is here.
Gary! Namaste!
Pied Piper incorporated
amended board of directors.
Richard Hendricks, Peter
Gregory... Erlich Bachman?
Oh, my God.
Is sleeping beauty awake?
Yes, she is.
Oh, boy. Here, I brought you
something for your stomach.
Be forewarned, the orange
juice has vodka in it.
Little hair of the dog.
What exactly happened last
night, from your side?
We happened, Richard. And the best part is,
we can relive it whenever we want to.
We're two halves of the same brain!
Whoa! You complete me!
Don't ever say that again!
Do you understand me?
I will beat the shit out of you.
Yo, yo, get that camera out my face.
- Come on, Mr... Ok, ok.
- Get the camera out my face!
- Look at this part.
- I'm asking this fat,
beautiful man
In front of God and the Flo Rider
and this white, weird cocaine statue
- to be on the Pied Piper board of directors.
- Yes!
- A thousand times, yes!
- He's doin' it!
- Shake on it.
- It's a deal.
Oh, no.
Plus, we have this for
the Pied Piper documentary
that we're eventually gonna make.
We're making history together, partner.
Are you dressed like Steve Jobs?
Oh, am I?
Well, I suppose Steve and I always
have shared a similar aesthetic.
Hey. Little help?
Oh. Ok.
- Here you go.
- Thanks, man.
- Sorry about the throw. Bursitis.
- Yeah.
Uh, so, you guys having a meeting up here?
No. Not exactly.
We're all currently... unassigned.
How about you?
- Yeah. Unassigned.
- Yeah.
That's cool.
Yeah.
How could you put Erlich on the board?
What were you thinking?
You don't put someone inside
the company on the board.
Then he and Peter Gregory can vote you out.
Yeah. You gotta find an outsider
you trust. Like your mom.
I'd put Erlich on the board
before my mom. Backstabbing bitch.
Guys, I was drunk, ok?
You know, I half-jokingly
said to Gilfoyle last night.
"It looks like Richard is
going to suck Erlich's dick."
But that would be
reasonable compared to this.
Richard, um, could I speak to you?
Ok. Yeah.
He's the least cool guy I've ever met.
I heard about what's been happening.
I have to say, I'm a little disappointed.
Yeah, I don't... I don't
know what I was thinking.
Yes. I mean, um,
is there a reason I wasn't
invited to the party?
Is there some sense that
I'm not part of the gang?
What? Uh, Jared.
Of course not. It was just an oversight.
I mean, we weren't even
sure if we were gonna go.
Uh-huh. And what was it like there?
Were there gelatin shots?
No. No, uh, it was stupid and loud.
Uh, honestly, you're better off.
I suppose. I had a fine night.
I... I had some palak paneer and I
watched a documentary about Liberia.
But then I woke up to this,
um, unexpected development.
Do you... do you really
want Erlich on the board?
- Because I'll support you...
- No. I don't. At all.
I was just drunk.
I don't know how to get out of it.
I mean, what am I going
to say to Peter Gregory?
Well, if you don't sign the documents,
and you don't give them to Peter Gregory,
then it won't happen. Simple as that.
Really? I... Wow. Ok.
That is a relief, Jared. Thanks.
I'm... I'm glad you're around.
Well, keep that in mind for future parties.
Honestly, sometimes we forget you're here.
- Oh...
- You guys, company photo time
out back. Let's go!
Uh, Gilfoyle, ok, off to
the center a little bit.
Like your personality. No, no, no, no.
Dinesh, leave it unbuttoned.
We want you to look like shit.
Makes for a better "before" photo.
But you're wearing a jacket.
Yeah, because I'm the genius marketer.
I'm not a code freak like you guys.
Besides, I'm wearing sandals so
I am iconoclasting a little bit.
Oh, good. Jared. Ugh. What
the fuck is with that vest?
Right over here. As if you're
sort of a late addition
that may not stick around for the
entire duration of the company.
And then, Richard. There
you go. The man of the hour.
Ok. We'll take a few like this,
and then... Just Richard and I.
Because at the end of the day,
people only want to see a
picture of the board members.
It... Actually, it's, um...
You're not gonna be a board member.
What?
I'm in year three of a five year deal
and, Matt, you got what,
like three years left?
Yeah. We all got acquired by Hooli,
when we didn't work out,
none of us got reassigned.
Because Gavin believes in this
Japanese form of management
where not being assigned is
the most shameful outcome.
Yeah, it does feel uncomfortable.
Nah. Give it a week or two,
you'll get, like, numb to it.
Well, why are you guys still coming in?
Rest and vest.
Oh... because in order to
fully vest your options,
you've gotta wait until
your contracts are up.
- I get it.
- You catch on slow.
You'll fit right in here.
Lunch? Arby's on El Camino? I'll drive.
No, let's walk. It'll take longer.
Gotta do something to fill the day, right?
I was drunk! You took advantage of me!
Man, they are really going at it.
So, um... last night, what
was the girl situation?
Shhh.
And after all I've given
up for this company.
Oh, what have you given up?
I owned ten percent of Dinesh's
app, ten percent of Gilfoyle's app.
- Multiple potential streams of income.
- Sure.
Not to mention that a
hundred percent of the team
that you have, were all guys
that I recruited for this house.
That must be worth something to me.
It is! Ten percent of Pied Piper!
For which I forewent,
yes, that's a real word,
- one million dollars.
- Mmm.
I supported you, Richard. I bet on you.
And now you're just gonna give me a seat
on the board, only to retract that offer?!
I can't even remember doing that!
Oh, really? Well, do you remember this
particular dick-bag I got on video?
Because you did.
Put it away.
It's right here.
Goddammit.
I've seen the video.
It's the wrong album, just give me a sec...
You know what? Fuck it!
You offering me a position
on this board and reneging it
is a perfect example of
you having no vision,
no balls and no game.
Maybe he did blow him.
Well, love and hate... It's all passion.
And if that's the kind
of company you wanna run,
well, then, fine.
God help you. 'Cause I sure as hell ain't.
Uh, what are you doing?
You give your loyalty to somebody...
- Let me help you.
- Don't touch!
- I can do it myself.
- All right.
I just put it back on. Goddammit!
Ok. Read that back to me.
"Pied Piper's mission is to bring
its unique compression algorithm
- to a variety..."
- One thing you should know about
living in this house is I do
not tolerate substance abuse.
There's no drinking and
lying in this house.
I should have made that more clear
to some of the current residents.
Like this one. Don't mind him.
He'll be gone soon when his
company cakes its pants.
Hopefully, Jurgen, you'll be able to bring
a more positive element to the house.
Let me show you the room I'm offering.
Some of his stuff is still in there,
but, as I mentioned, it will soon be gone.
Once his company cakes its pants.
It's ok. Just take a breath.
It's fine. I'm fine. Uh, we just...
Let's get through this. Ok,
so, read this back to me.
- "Pied Piper's mission..."
- Hey, guys.
Hope you don't mind, the
front door was just open.
Hi, Big Head. What's up?
Honestly? Nothing. I've just
been sitting around all day.
Not working. It's weird, you know?
Yeah.
So, what's up with you guys?
We're just sort of...
We're getting ready for this
big Peter Gregory meeting.
And we have... we have a
lot of work to do, so...
Cool. Very cool.
You know, Richard, the irony is that
if you had taken the ten million,
you'd be kicking back with a ton of
money right now and I'd still be working.
But you didn't, obviously. And
now I've got nothing to do,
I'm rolling in it, and
you're working your ass off.
Life's funny isn't it?
You guys want to walk to Arby's,
maybe grab a bite, play
a little hacky sack?
Yeah. I should probably
get back to work, anyway.
I mean, not work, exactly, I don't...
I don't work. But, you know,
just get back to Hooli.
Sit around all day and get paid
a bunch of money to do nothing.
Weird.
You ready?
You know what you're going to
say? You want to run it by me?
No, no. I got this. Fuck Erlich.
You know, I turned down ten million
dollars to build this thing.
You want vision, I will
show you fucking vision.
I like this new angry side to you.
Being around angry people relaxes me,
because I know where I stand.
Oh, shoot. I think I got
something stuck in my teeth.
I'm just gonna go to the bathroom,
check it out. I'll be back in a sec.
Richard, it's Jared. Are you ok?
Hey buddy, what's... going on here?
I thought I had something in my teeth,
but when I looked over, right? I
looked in the mirror like this,
uh, my pants they hit the countertop,
and it must have some
water on there, right?
So I got a spot on my pants, kinda looked
like I pissed myself like a big baby.
So what I did was, I just
took off all my pants
and I put it in the water just
to make it all completely wet.
You know, that way I figured
no one would really notice.
So, you know, it wouldn't be as
bad. I've got it under control.
I've sorted it out. We're good.
Yes. So you felt this wouldn't look as bad.
- Understood.
- Yeah.
But, Richard? Um...
Consider that maybe this might not
be the best choice for the meeting?
Yeah. Holy...
What the fuck am I doing?
I can't go like this to the meeting.
Jared. I have no vision.
Yes, you do.
- I believe in you...
- No, no, I literally have no vision.
All I see is stars and swirls.
I cannot see right now.
Ok, let's get your pants on.
Jared? Richard? Are you in there?
Ohh.
Hey, there's some weather over the ocean
so Peter would love to get
started. Are you guys ready?
Yep. All good. Be there in a jiffy.
- Ok.
- Oh.
Jared, I'm on a carpet in a bathroom.
Yeah, ok. Um, I know this
isn't the best thing to say
to someone having a panic attack,
but we need to hurry here.
- Doing ok?
- Yes, much better.
Nope. Worse.
Richard, you're gonna listen to me
if you know what's good for you.
- Erlich.
- I may have been wrong
about being a board member
and I may be wrong about being the
Steve Jobs in our relationship.
But I do know this, you
are the Steve Wozniak.
And no Woz should go into
a meeting like that alone.
- No. Actually...
- So if you'll just let me come in,
then I won't speak.
And I just think you should
have somebody in there
who will actually have your back.
Ok. No, I... Erlich, I
want you to be in there.
Ok... wait, what?
Yes, and I need you to do all the talking.
Because I feel like if I do I'm
gonna puke all over Peter Gregory.
Oh, ok. Wow.
That was easier than I... All the talking?
Oh, Erlich, you're here too?
- Ok. Come on in, guys.
- Um, I'm going to stay here, I think.
Because I look absurd.
Yeah. Yeah, ok.
- So what are you going to say?
- Fuck, I don't know.
Today's user wants access
to all of their files
from all their devices instantly.
That's why cloud-based is the holy grail.
Now Dropbox is winning,
but when it comes to audio and video files,
they might as well be called Dripbox.
Using our platform, Pied Piper users
would be able to compress all their files
to the point where they truly
can access them instantly.
We control the pipe,
they just use it.
That's the vision in
Richard Hendricks' head.
Sure.
Sounds fine.
Oh, I received an email from Ron Laflamme
saying that this gentleman
is going to be our third board member?
Uhh...
Yes. Yes.
Uh, Erlich helped me with all
this stuff. He's very talented.
I need him as a partner.
Fine.
It's ok for you to leave now.
All right, ok.
Wait, is that you and Gavin Belson?
Yes. It's an old photograph.
Were you guys friends?
I thought so.
Good-bye.
How'd it go?
That was amazing. I mean, that was like
everything in my head but, like, clear.
Did you just make that up on the spot?
Yeah. We should probably
write some of it down.
Yeah. Well, look. I gotta be honest,
I mean, I can't tell
you how much this means.
You really saved my ass even
after I was such a dick to you.
- You're making up!
- What else could I do, Richard?
You're my Wozniak.
And I will always be...
Motherfu...
☯Synced & Corrected by Seppuku17☯
❃www.addic7ed.com❃
www.tvsubtitles.net