It's a fucking sketchy neighborhood, man.
You see that guy? That's Chuy Ramirez.
And he's gonna do our new logo.
That's the artist you were talking about?
You said he had paintings in galleries.
His works hang in the
gallery of the streets.
- I'll be back in a flash.
- Whoa, no. What?
OK.
Man, we're just going
to sit here like this?
Oh, shit. Look at this guy.
He's a scary individual.
- Whoa. Um...
- Hey, buddy. Do you have any drugs?
Please, let it up. Let it up.
If you don't let it go, I can't roll it up.
Just... please... Just, you...
Fucking prick! Ow!
I'm gonna beat you in your face!
Chuy Ramirez? Erlich Bachman.
- We spoke on the phone?
- What's up, man?
- Pleasure to meet you.
- All right.
This is great. Look at this.
This is what we need, you know
what I mean? Something raw.
We already have kind of a
shitty name, Pied Piper,
but the last thing we want is
two lowercase P's in a square
like those motherfuckers
across the freeway would make.
This is what we want?
So you gonna give me
stock options, or what?
- What?
- Yeah. You know Dave Cho?
He did the murals over at Facebook.
He got a stock option deal, ended up
making like a hundred million dollars.
I want a deal like that.
You know, I don't really speak
all that Wall Street bullshit.
You know what I'm saying?
We're just like five guys
hanging out in a house,
trying to make cool shit.
Well, you told me you
own ten percent of it,
so you must know something about it, right?
You could just give me some of your points.
Hey, I'm not an accountant, you know?
I don't even know what that means,
a lot of those words.
You fucking prick!
Oh, you fucker.
Let me in. Please, please...
I'll break this. I don't
care. I don't care.
- I'll break this...
- I can't hear you.
Oh God.
I can't hear you.
Yeah, but you don't want
stock in our company.
If I could go back in time, I
wouldn't have taken the stock.
I would've taken cash
only. I'm telling you...
Who's that dude?
- Uh, nobody. He's a coder.
- You got a Latino working for you?
That's cool, yo. Not a lot
of Latinos working in tech.
Yeah. Yeah, he's Latino.
Yeah, and he's one of
the best coders we have.
Kind of adds a Latin flair to the company.
I told you, we do things differently.
Yeah. You know what?
I could do a cash deal
for a Latino company.
I think we should get out of here, though,
because I just painted
over some dude's shit
and people get shot behind that.
So I'll catch you on the flip. Peace!
Uh, OK. Peace, Chuy.
Oh, God. This is...
This is very real!
Hey, Dinesh! Get in the fucking car.
There may be a drive-by about to happen.
What?
☯Synced & Corrected by Seppuku17☯
❃www.addic7ed.com❃
You promised this guy ten thousand dollars
without any approval?
- Are you high?
- A little bit, yeah.
But that's irrelevant.
A cool company needs a cool logo.
You think those guys over
at Nucleus are hiring
a convicted felon to paint
a mural on their garage?
For ten thousand dollars? No.
Look, I took a run at a burn-down chart.
Jesus fucking Christ.
It's not pretty.
The way things are going,
we're not gonna finish for five months,
and even with everyone on reduced salaries,
we'll exhaust all our funding in four.
And that's without wasting ten
thousand dollars on artwork.
"Wasting"? I got a great deal.
You know he wanted stock
options until he saw Dinesh?
- Hold on, what?
- Don't be offended,
but for some weird reason,
Chuy took a look at you
and thought you were... a Mexican.
Why would I be offended by that?
- What?
- Why would I be offended
by him thinking I'm Mexican?
He's Mexican, right?
Yeah, he is, but you're
not. You're Pakistani.
So? Actually,
the very fact that you think
this would be offensive to me
is offensive.
You're the one being racist.
No. I'm not the one who
called you a Mexican.
"Called me a Mexican"?
You're doing it again.
I'm bending over backwards
to not be racist right now.
All right. Well, what did he say
when you told him I wasn't Mexican?
- I didn't.
- And why not?
Because I wanted him to
paint our garage for cheap.
I... I genuinely don't know
how to respond to that.
You know, I'm not gonna take the bait here.
I am not a racist, all right?
I watch a lot of black porn. I mean, a lot.
One question.
In this porn, is the man black,
or the woman black, or are they both?
Is one of those racist,
and the others aren't?
I'll hack his browser history.
We'll get to the bottom of this.
Yep.
Hold on. That's unnecessary.
Hold on.
Richard?
Can you explain this to me?
Hmm? What?
I just got a text from
my friend at TechCrunch.
Pied Piper just got into this
year's Start-Up Battlefield?
Oh, really? Oh, that's so cool.
No. No, it isn't. We're
already seeded, Richard.
Why would we enter a start-up
competition at a tech conference?
I sent in the application a few months ago
and I totally forgot about it.
Relax, I will withdraw.
Relax? This house is chaos.
I gave up a great job and stock
options at Hooli to come here
because I thought Pied
Piper could be viable,
but it never will be unless
we make some changes.
We need to operate like a business
or we're not going to...
Richard? Richard?
Thanks for coming in, Nelson.
Mr. Belson is very
excited to meet with you.
I thought he was in Jackson Hole this week.
Yes, he is. We're going to
call him up on the TeleHuman.
It's amazing. It's holographic 3D
teleconferencing technology that we've acquired.
It's going to feel as
if Gavin is right here
in the room with you.
Oh, it's him!
It's him!
Hello, Nelson. Thanks for meeting with me.
Whoa. Hi. That's cool.
Am I a hologram over there too?
What? No, of course not.
do you still talk to Richard Hendricks?
Uh, yeah. I mean, not about
Nucleus or anything...
Why would he enter Pied
Piper in TechCrunch Disrupt?
I know a lot of big players
have come out of it,
Dropbox, Yammer, what have you.
But Peter Gregory's already funding him.
Why would he let Richard
do this? It makes no sense.
I don't know. I didn't
even know Richard got in.
Is Peter Gregory toying with me?
Is he trying to make Richard seem folksy?
Like some aw-shucks boy-genius
entering an everyman's competition?
Mr. Bel... Mr. Belson?
- Can you hear me?
- Hello?
- Yeah, it's just...
- It's sort of fading.
- Hel-l-l-lo?
- Hello.
- Hello-ooo.
I'm hearing you, it's just the image is...
Nelson, shut up for a second.
If you can hear me, make a gesture.
Is that... do you... I hear you.
- Is this...
- I have no idea what you're saying, Nelson.
...Nelson. Nelson.
Can you help me, please?
OK, I think what happened
was when you set it up,
- you forgot to...
- I didn't set it up.
I paid one of you people
to set it up. Just fix it.
Uh... OK.
Here's the thing, it's not working.
Um, the audio's still working.
You could just use that.
"The audio is working"? Excuse me?!
I paid twenty million fucking
dollars to acquire this company!
Fuck you, the audio is working!
Audio worked a hundred fucking years ago!
You fucking piece of shit-t-t-t...
- It appears we've lost him.
- Yeah.
- Why don't we just Hooli-Chat instead?
Ah. That's better.
Sorry. The TeleHuman is a
great piece of technology.
Unfortunately, the broadband isn't
that great out here in rural Wyoming.
That presents a great business opportu...
Nelson, make a gesture... hear me.
Oh, for fuck's sake.
Uh... I think you forgot
to update your software.
God dammit. Fu...!
Oh.
Hello. Oh, hi, Gavin.
What's that? I'm sorry,
you're kind of breaking up there.
He... Hello? Hello?
OK, let's start the meeting.
I think we need to define
our corporate culture.
Our whole corporate culture
is that we don't have
a corporate culture.
That is totally ridiculous, Gilfoyle.
The main reason dogs are perceived to have
a more keen sense of smell is because
their noses are closer to the ground.
Therefore, with a little practice,
I could easily have as keen
a sense of smell as a dog's.
Guys? I guess you didn't see the sign.
We're actually having a meeting here.
Congratulations.
It's sort of for management only.
Are you fucking serious right now?
Are you really kicking us out?
Well, I thought, maybe you guys could just
take your food into the living room?
So you want to have a meeting in
the room where all the food is,
while we eat our food in the room
where all of the computers are?
Guys, just five minutes. Please?
OK, you see? This...
This is a case in point.
This is a company,
and yet we have no
boundaries and no protocol.
We need to establish a
clear corporate culture
or we're not gonna make it.
Take Dinesh and Gilfoyle.
They are wasting an enormous
amount of time arguing.
What if we were to separate them, right?
Divide their existing
work space into two areas.
We could put in some kind
of portable barrier...
He's talking about cubicles!
We are not doing cubicles. No way!
No, no, no. Don't think of it as a cubicle.
Just think of it as a
neutral-colored enclosure,
about yay-high, around your workspace.
OK, fine. But do you
know who uses cubicles?
Every single Fortune 500 company.
Why? Because they work.
He's trying to turn us into
corporate rock, Richard.
- No.
- We are punk rock.
Actually, you know, I think a
better analogy would be jazz.
Like we riff and improvise
around a central theme
to create one cohesive piece of music...
No, no. They teach
fucking jazz at Juilliard.
We're not jazz. We're fucking punk rock.
You see? You see, you guys are arguing over
what metaphor to use to
agree with each other.
This is the inefficiency
I'm trying to eliminate.
My suggestions could actually
help you beat me in this argument.
Do you see the irony there?
I... I can't argue with this.
Yo, Erlich!
Uh, Chuy's here.
No. And this, this... This
is the craziest one of all.
I mean, we're really about
to spend ten thousand dollars
on-on-on a logo we could
generate in-house for free?
It's madness. You want a logo?
Here, just...
There. I just saved this
company ten thousand dollars.
Are you fucking serious? Lowercase letters?
Twitter: lowercase "t".
Google: lowercase "g".
Facebook: lowercase "f".
Every fucking company in the
Valley has lowercase letters.
Why? Because it's safe.
But we aren't going to do that.
We're gonna go with Chuy.
Unless any of you gringos
wants to go out there
and tell a guy with
three assault convictions
that we're not gonna give him
the money we promised him.
Hm? That's what I thought.
I mean... God.
Are you still enjoying your asparagus, sir?
I was never enjoying it.
I only eat it for the nutrients.
You may take it.
Oh, shit.
Peter, I don't want to upset you,
but Gavin Belson just walked in.
Does he see us?
I don't know. He must
know that you're here.
If I scurry to the restroom,
do you imagine he would...
Peter!
I didn't know you came here.
Gavin. Hello.
Nice to see you.
And you, as well.
How are you?
Well.
And you?
Not bad.
I just got back from Jackson Hole.
Have you been?
I have not.
But I hear good things.
You look well. Are you exercising?
I have begun to do Pilates.
Well... I hear that's good.
I like it.
Yes.
Well, I didn't mean to interrupt.
Nice to see you, Peter.
- Goodbye now.
- OK.
You know, I almost forgot.
I saw that Pied Piper
is in the Start-Up Battlefield
at TechCrunch Disrupt.
It inspired me to call TechCrunch
and offer to be their keynote speaker.
They were quite accommodating.
Especially when I said
that I'd make the event
the grand unveiling of Nucleus.
So, I will see you all at the conference.
This is displeasing.
I have never seen him so incensed.
What the hell were you thinking, Richard?
How could you not tell us you
entered TechCrunch Disrupt?
I applied before I even met you guys.
I wasn't gonna say anything
because I was gonna withdraw.
- No, you're not.
- I'm not? Why not?
Because of you, Gavin Belson
is debuting Nucleus at TCD.
If you pull out, it looks like
Peter is running away from Gavin.
So like it or not, you
are presenting a live demo
in front of the world in eight weeks.
A live demo of what?
I entered TCD with an
early build of Pied Piper,
when it was still just a music app.
No. Sorry. Executive decision,
we are not doing TechCrunch.
OK. So let me just tell
you what's gonna happen.
Peter will pull all of his support
and pass on any further funding,
which, as you know, is the most
flaming signaling risk on earth.
You'll burn through the
rest of your runway,
no one will step in, then you'll go bust.
I don't get it.
Doesn't Peter Gregory want
what's best for the company?
Look. I'm going to be straight with you.
Peter Gregory doesn't care.
- About...?
- You.
Wait. Just him or both of us?
Any of you. Pied Piper.
OK...
Uh, well, then why did he back us?
Does he just want to piss off Gavin Belson?
- He spent two hundred thousand dollars just to...
- Yeah, that's nothing!
Peter would spend millions
just to mildly annoy Gavin.
These are billionaires, Richard.
Humiliating each other
is worth more to them
than we'll make in a lifetime.
I see.
And you conveniently forgot
to mention any of this
when you were convincing me
to turn down ten million dollars?
And now I'm in the middle
of some pissing contest
between two billionaires.
In fairness,
Gavin only offered you
the ten million dollars
because we started pursuing you...
But he offered it to me,
Monica! He offered it to me.
Ten million dollars and I didn't take it.
Because you came to me when
I was puking and freaking out
and told me that Peter
Gregory believed in me,
when in reality, he didn't
even give a flying fuck!
- Richard...
- Oh, my God.
I didn't turn down ten million dollars
because of Peter Gregory, Monica!
I turned it down because of you!
However angry he is, I
am one-tenth as angry.
Because one of the ten
million would've been mine.
- Because I... I own ten percent.
- I know.
- Of Pied Piper...
- I know!
It's push.
We didn't think we were
going to get this thing done
when we had five months
to do it. Now we have two?
Granted, it's not ideal, but
we're just gonna have to...
What the good fuck?
What is happening? Is that Dinesh?
Is that the Statue of Liberty?
And it's... There's penetration.
Oh! Hey, neighbor.
- Ashley's getting big!
- Aw.
She looks... What do we do?
I don't know. Paint over it.
No, no, no. You can't paint over it.
It's like the code of the streets.
People get shot behind that.
- Oh, good.
- Hey. So what do you guys think, man?
Uhh... I think Erlich had a few thoughts.
So, I gotta... I'll let you...
Uhh...
Here's the headline:
there's a lot right with it.
A lot of good stuff in there.
But I just...
Do you think the piece is working?
I mean... Maybe it's a bit
too graphic for the space?
No way. Look at it.
It comments on the Latino
struggle for justice in America.
But even without all the symbolism,
it's just aesthetically pleasing.
Yeah.
All right, here's the real shit, Chuy.
Uh, you know, our prize coder,
he's actually not... Latino.
What?
Yeah. Point of fact is, he's Pakistani.
Homes, you lied to me.
No, no, no. You thought he was Latino,
and I thought I would be racist
telling you, you were wrong.
Come on, man. Why would you think that?
Thinking that, now that's racist.
God, I can't win... with that.
Look, Chuy, painting a
guy named Dinesh Chugtai
as an Aztec warrior
just doesn't make sense.
Yeah. You know what?
I think you might be right, boss.
Great. That's...
So... Perfect. So change that
and then don't have him be fucking
the literal symbol of freedom.
And then, whatever else you wanna do.
- All right.
If I had known, we could have withdrawn your
application before any of this happened.
This is exactly why we need to have
clearer lines of communication.
I know, Jared, I know.
Listen, I'd like to institute
an organizational system called "scrum."
Scrum is designed to...
All right, you have one hour! Go!
No.
No. Just musty.
Uhh, what's going on?
Gilfoyle bet me a hundred bucks
that if I touched one object in this room,
he could find it just by sniffing.
OK. Not now, please.
It has to be now. I just
masturbated to heighten my focus.
I have a fifteen-minute refractory period.
- Ow.
- Uhh, well, we have a lot of work to get done
- So maybe we should do that instead, please.
- Dude, relax, OK?
We each ripped through a
full module this morning.
We're just taking a little break.
DRM is now a thing of beauty.
Wait. You did DRM?
- Yeah.
- I did DRM.
Why did you do DRM? I said I would
do DRM, you would do error handling.
Anything to do with "error"
sounds like your whole vibe.
- Yeah, I handle errors like you every day.
- Scrum?
- Yes, scrum.
- Scrum.
So from "rules based filtering"
we got to "workflow,"
at which point that card
is moved from the "icebox"
into the "in progress"
column and it stays there
until it is ready for "testing."
OK. This increases visibility
into our team's progress.
And that, gentlemen, is scrum.
Welcome to the next
eight weeks of our lives.
This just became a job.
OK, so here are the cards
I'm adding under this epic
for the ingestion engine.
And there are three stories here.
How long do we think each one will take?
I don't know. Who cares? Four hours apiece?
Yeah. Maybe for you.
Each of those tasks
would take me three max.
Not "tasks," "stories."
I've got a story, why don't
you choke on my balls?
Well, how about this?
Why don't you each take one story, right...
and we'll see who's right?
You see what he's doing, right?
He's trying to get us to
compete so we work faster.
He thinks this wall of Psych
101, MBA mind-control bullshit
is going to motivate us?
Fine. Don't compete. Do them
at whatever speed you like.
Uh, Jared.
Uh... I know these guys.
I really don't think scrum
is gonna work for them.
Whoa... Just trust in the system.
So we're just going to work at
a nice, leisurely pace, right?
Sure.
Wait, why are you typing faster?
I'm not.
Maybe my leisurely pace is just
a little faster than yours.
Cock-sucker.
Boo-yah.
Guys? Have you been out front yet?
'Cause you might wanna come see this.
- I'm good.
- Fuck off, we're working.
Wow. This took a lot of work.
I mean, I'm already smiling.
Did he really have to paint
me giving the thumbs-up?
It's gratuitous.
Really? That's the gratuitous part?
Well, and Dinesh's shaft...
- Oh, no.
- Uh...
Oh shit.
Are one of you the homeowner?
Yeah. I am.
We've had a number of complaints
about your artwork here.
Look, what you do inside the
house is your own business...
- Oh, no. We don't... We don't do that.
- Oh, no!
But that is you, is it not?
The individual on the right?
Yeah.
You're gonna need to paint over this.
Oh, I don't think the artist
would like that, he's Latino.
- Was that racist?
- Why are you asking me?
Oh. I mean, I could've asked
anybody, but your... race...
It doesn't matter. I have a solution.
We put it up.
We don't put it down. Leave it up.
No, no, no. No, no, no! Close it!
No...
Look at this... left
from the previous tenant.
Unbelievable. I can't believe
I didn't enter the garage until this point.
I mean, is that marijuanas?
We're gonna need to take those.
Or, we leave them and wait to see
if the criminal returns
to the scene of the crime.
What do you say, please?
OK. So I keep the mural,
and I keep the ten G's.
What do you get?
I just thought when I
got a new garage door,
maybe you could come and paint a new logo.
Something just as artistic,
but maybe a little less challenging?
Hey! Don't look under
there. Get away from there!
That's not me.
Um, just to be honest with you, like,
I really, really, really need this.
So... I'm trying to be
vulnerable in front of you.
I don't know. Is this a safe place?
Look, you can be vulnerable, esé,
but this ain't a safe place.
A plumber got stabbed just last week,
right where you're standing.
What?! Jesus Christ!
What... Why would you stab a plumber?
All right. It was worth a try.
Thanks anyway, Chuy.
Wait. Just go ahead and leave the mural.
I like looking at it.
And plus, I think I know what kind
of logo you white boys might like.
Uh, that's amazing. Thank you, Chuy!
- Uh, yeah. Appreciate it.
- All right, man.
- Yes, one of those too.
- All right.
- Another one down.
- Did you really?
You still working on that last one?
Take your time. There's no rush, Dinesh.
Feeling pretty happy about yourself?
I'm pretty happy with ourself.
Hello?
Hey, is... Is Richard here?
I don't know.
- Hey.
Come to check up on your investment?
Listen, you were right.
I played you a little.
Maybe a lot. I got caught
up in making the deal.
All right? And I would like to
say I was just doing my job,
but that's the excuse that the Nazis used,
so I'm not really sure
how effective that one is.
Your point being?
I'm sorry.
But I'm also not sorry.
The reason I pushed Peter to seed you is,
I think you have an
unbelievably good platform.
Way better than the rest of
his other compression plays,
which I apologize for
not telling you about.
Look, I know eight weeks
isn't a lot of time
to get this ready,
but I get the feeling you're
the kind of guy that does better
when there's a fire lit under his ass.
It's a pretty big fire.
It is.
And by the way,
you're the only one of Peter's companies
that I've invested ten percent
of my annual salary in.
So I really hope that you can do this.
Uh, well, you know,
I guess we'll find out.
I saw the logo out front.
I didn't know it was...
Cool. Guys, the new logo!
- Can we please both go?
- You go first.
I love it.
Well, it's lowercase,
but at least it isn't racist.
Is it?
It's Chuy Ramirez? I'm impressed.
He sold a mural today
for a half-million bucks.
It wasn't on a garage door, was it?
You don't think it's too
incendiary for the offices?
Kevin, you got where you are
by challenging sensibilities.
You know me well.
It is pretty raunchy, though.
☯Synced & Corrected by Seppuku17☯
❃www.addic7ed.com❃
www.tvsubtitles.net